export const algoDailyDictionary = {
  problems: [
    {
      description: "Distribute Candies",
      date: "September 28, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/distribute-candies/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/uniqueness-of-arrays.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Remove Duplicates From Array",
      date: "September 27, 2021",
      problem: "https://algodaily.com/challenge_slides/uniqueness-of-arrays",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/uniqueness-of-arrays.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Sum All Primes",
      date: "September 26, 2021",
      problem: "https://algodaily.com/challenge_slides/sum-all-primes",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/sum-all-primes.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Missing Ranges",
      date: "September 15, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/missing-ranges/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/missing_ranges.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Single Number",
      date: "September 14, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/single-number/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/single_number.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Power of Three",
      date: "September 13, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/power-of-three/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/power_of_three.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Majority Element",
      date: "September 12, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/majority-element/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/majority_element.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Valid Palindrome",
      date: "September 12, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-palindrome/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/valid_palindrome.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Valid Anagram",
      date: "September 12, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-anagram/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/valid_anagram.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Reverse Only Letters",
      date: "September 12, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-only-letters",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/reverse_only_letters.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Fizz Buzz",
      date: "September 12, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/fizz-buzz/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/intersection_of_two_arrays.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Array Intersection",
      date: "September 12, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/intersection-of-two-arrays/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/intersection_of_two_arrays.cpp"
    },
    {
      description: "Reverse a String",
      date: "September 12, 2021",
      problem: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-string/",
      answer:
        "https://github.com/palak-dhingra/algo-daily/blob/main/coding-solution/reverse_string.cpp"
    }
  ],
  quotes: [
    {
      quote:
        "Most software today is very much like an Egyptian pyramid with millions of bricks piled on top of each other, with no structural integrity, but just done by brute force and thousands of slaves.",
      author: "Alan Kay"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "There are two major products that come out of Berkeley: LSD and UNIX. We don’t believe this to be a coincidence.",
      author: "Jeremy S. Anderson"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "PHP is a minor evil perpetrated and created by incompetent amateurs, whereas Perl is a great and insidious evil, perpetrated by skilled but perverted professionals.",
      author: "Jon Ribbens"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "“Doing less is not being lazy. Don't give in to a culture that values personal sacrifice over personal productivity.”",
      author: "Tim Ferriss"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "There are only two kinds of programming languages: those people always bitch about and those nobody uses.",
      author: "Bjarne Stroustrup"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "“Someday” is a disease that will take your dreams to the grave with you.”",
      author: "Tim Ferriss"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "XML is like violence – if it doesn’t solve your problems, you are not using enough of it.",
      author: "Unknown"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "No matter how slick the demo is in rehearsal, when you do it in front of a live audience, the probability of a flawless presentation is inversely proportional to the number of people watching, raised to the power of the amount of money involved.",
      author: "Mark Gibbs"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "“The opposite of love is indifference, and the opposite of happiness is boredom.”",
      author: "Tim Ferriss"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I’m not sure about the universe.",
      author: "Albert Einstein"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "“For all of the most important things, the timing always sucks. Waiting for a good time to quit your job? The stars will never align and the traffic lights of life will never all be green at the same time. The universe doesn't conspire against you, but it doesn't go out of its way to line up the pins either. Conditions are never perfect. “Someday” is a disease that will take your dreams to the grave with you. Pro and con lists are just as bad. If it's important to you and you want to do it “eventually,” just do it and correct course along the way.”",
      author: "Tim Ferriss"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "We know about as much about software quality problems as they knew about the Black Plague in the 1600s. We’ve seen the victims’ agonies and helped burn the corpses. We don’t know what causes it; we don’t really know if there is only one disease. We just suffer — and keep pouring our sewage into our water supply.",
      author: "Tom Van Vleck"
    },
    {
      quote:
        "“The goal is to create a “chit,” or IOU, so that, assuming you continue to perform well, the organization feels like it owes you the next time.”",
      author: "Carla Harris"
    }
  ]
};
